(Raj:)...just reminds me too much of India.
I haven't been since I was a kid.
We should go one weekend.
(Bernadette:)Weekends are too crowded.
- So blow off work, go on a weekday.
- Hooky?
(Amy:)I've never played hooky in my life.
(Amy:)My mom said that's how girls end up
addicted to reefer and jazz music.
(Penny:)More like how girls end up
at a Best Western hotel...
(Penny:)...with a 34-year-old guy named Luther.
- Joke?
- I can laugh about it now.
(Bernadette:)What do you say? This Friday
we ditch work and go to Disneyland?
- I'm in.
- Me too.
(Raj:)Excuse me, I thought we were
trying to solve my problem.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, right.
(Penny:)Wait, what was your problem again?
I'm a man who can't talk to women, trying
to figure out how to go on a romantic date...
...with a girl who suffers from social
anxiety, she can't be around other people.
(Penny:)Yeah, that's a toughie.